<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="about_tarot">
	&lt;h3>Tarot and Cognition&lt;/h3>
	&lt;p>The meaning of tarot is not at all straightforward. On its face a tarot deck is simply 78 cards, broken into two arcana - the major and the minor.  The major arcana consists of 22 cards in a sequence; the minor arcana is more like a traditional deck of playing cards (which tarot is closely related to) with four suits of pips (number cards) and court cards.&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>The suits of the minor arcana convey aspects of human life represented by swords: the ruling class, cups: the mythmakers - clergy and artists, coins: the merchants, and wands: the working class. The major arcana on the other hand conveys a tale of life\&quot;s journey through darkness and redemption.&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>For more about the history of the tarot deck visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://trionfi.com/&quot;>the Trionfi Museum&lt;/a>
&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>The mysteries and ambiguities begin to emerge when one considers the meanings and purpose of the cards. Many tarot readers place mystical significance on the cards claiming that they are able to draw upon a person\&quot;s energy to reveal hidden aspects of their lives and / or future. This school of thought places a lot of significance on the questioner actively handling the cards either through shuffling, cutting the deck, or selecting the cards for the spread.&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>Having such a view it would be hard to conceive of an effective software tarot, at least until the advent of smartphones. With smartphones you have highly personal devices that are carried by the questioner the majority of the day at least. It would follow that the same sort of energy exchange would occur under these conditions as with handling cards, and perhaps even more so.&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>The entire subject of energetic or subconscious transference is quite irrelevant however, because regardless of energy transfer spending time with tarot is beneficial for cognition.&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>The cognitive model of tarot holds that the cards of the deck are representative of abstract and archetypal patterns of human experience. Generic and vague descriptions or models of things we all experience in life, often things that are always present in some form. Thus the cards provide a variety of angles from which a question or situation can be viewed.&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>In doing a tarot reading the questioner is actually stepping back to consider some issue or question from a randomly drawn set of human archetypes. In essence it is a way to force oneself to consider a number of alternative perspectives on any challenging topic.&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>From this model the tarot reading the accuracy is not as relevant a factor as taking a broader view of things prior to acting. It is a tool for tapping into your own experiences and knowledge through triggering these archetypes in relation to the subject at hand.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3>Choosing a spread&lt;/h3>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>The first step in using TarotBot is choosing a spread.The options are:&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The Arrow of Time&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>Dialectic&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>Pentagram&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>Chaos Star&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The Celtic Cross&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>BOTA&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>For all spreads except for BOTA, selection launches you directly into the spread.&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;h3>The Arrow of Time&lt;/h3>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>The traditional past, present, and future&lt;/p>
	&lt;h3>Dialectic&lt;/h3>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>Based on the Hegelian dialectic commonly represented as thesis, antithesis, and synthesis.&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>from Wikipedia:&lt;/p>
	&lt;blockquote>comprising three dialectical stages of development: a thesis, giving rise to its reaction, an antithesis, which contradicts or negates the thesis, and the tension between the two being resolved by means of a synthesis.&lt;/blockquote>
	&lt;h3>Pentagram&lt;/h3>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>Based on a spread described by &lt;a href=&quot;http://tarahelios.wordpress.com/&quot;>Paul Pereira&lt;/a> in a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.paganspace.net/forum/topics/favorite-tarot-spreads&quot;>discussion about tarot spreads&lt;/a>
&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>1 - Fire - Related to action/activities/will
	&lt;br/>2- Water - relationships/emotional aspects
	&lt;br/>3- Air - thoughts/conflict
	&lt;br/>4- Earth - career/money/practical aspects
	&lt;br/>5- spiritual dimension&lt;/p>
	&lt;h3>Chaos Star&lt;/h3>
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;p>Adapted from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://ritualchaosmagic.blogspot.com/2009/11/chaos-star-tarot-spread.html&quot;>Ritual and Chaos Magic blog&lt;/a> post by &lt;a href=&quot;http://enfolding.org/&quot;>Phil Hine&lt;/a>
&lt;/p>
	&lt;blockquote>Select eight cards from your shuffled pack.
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;br/>Lay them out as in the diagram above. Here is what the position of each card can be used to represent:
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;br/>1 - (Red) External Conflicts
	&lt;br/>2 - (Orange) Mental State
	&lt;br/>3 - (Purple) Sex/Passion
	&lt;br/>4 - (Yellow) Ego/Self Confidence
	&lt;br/>5 - (Green) Love/Relationships
	&lt;br/>6 - (Blue) Wealth
	&lt;br/>7 - (Black) Self Destructive Habits
	&lt;br/>8 - (Octarine) Your \&quot;Magical Self\&quot; (this would be \&quot;luck\&quot; if reading for a non-magician)&lt;/blockquote>
	&lt;h3>The Celtic Cross&lt;/h3>
	&lt;p>
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sacred-texts.com/tarot/pkt/pkt0307.htm&quot;>First recorded&lt;/a> by A.E.Waite a good &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.learntarot.com/ccross.htm&quot;>modern interpretation of the celtic cross&lt;/a> has also been published by Joan Bunning
	&lt;br/>
	&lt;br/>from Wikipedia:&lt;/p>
	&lt;br/>
&lt;blockquote>
	&lt;p>This is probably the most common spread. Ten cards are used, with five arranged in a cross and four placed  vertically beside the cross. Another card is placed horizontally across  the central cards of the cross to make a total of 10.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The first central  card of the cross is frequently the significator and the second card  which is placed over the first represents the conditions surrounding the  question; or the crossing card often represents an obstacle they must  face, an aspect of the question they have not yet considered.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The third  card which is placed above the first represents what the person hopes  for in relation to the question being asked.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The fourth card which is  placed below the first is what the subject has already experienced in  relation to the whole spread.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The fifth card is placed to the left of  the first card and shows what was in the past.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The sixth card is placed  to the right of the first card and shows the influence that will come in  the future.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>Then on the right of these cards are the remaining 4 cards,  which are placed from bottom to top. So the seventh card represents the  attitude of the question being asked.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The eighth card is how family or  friends will influence the question.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The ninth card shows the hopes and  fears in relation to the question and the final card, the tenth card, is  the Culmination Card which shows the end result of all of the previous  nine cards.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
	&lt;h3>BOTA&lt;/h3>
	&lt;p>The BOTA spread is based on the reading described in the book &lt;a href=&quot;http://tarotinstitute.com/free/bota/oracle.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>The Oracle of the Tarot&lt;/a> by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.golden-dawn.org/biocase.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Paul Foster Case&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The basic process works like this:&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>A significator card is chosen based upon a birth date, sex and relationship status&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The full tarot deck is shuffled&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The deck is cut in half&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>Each resulting deck is then cut in half&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>Which ever deck contains the significator is then dealt in a circle&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>Starting with the significator, some number of cards around the circle is counted (the number counted depends on which significator is used)&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>The card landed on is the next card in the reading&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>Starting with the last card of the reading, some number of cards around the circle is counted (the number counted depends on the previously landed on card)&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>Steps 7 and 8 are repeated until the same card is landed on twice&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>If this last card is the significator it means the reading is particularly personal, otherwise the last card is the most significant card of the reading&lt;/p>
</string>
<string name="about_app">
	&lt;h1>TarotBot塔罗牌程序&lt;/h1>
	&lt;p>TarotBot是一 开源程序 Android设备上配有塔罗牌占卜程序及诠释.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>界面, 就是塔罗牌, 最初的设计创意是一种古老的艺术设计 (塔罗牌) 的属性，对阅读很有意义: 意象, 诠释, 和上下文. 传统的洗牌, 发牌, 和重新发牌等这些已经从TarotBot程序中取消。精简占卜和阅读体验。. 用塔罗牌TaroBot程序可能不同于现实生活的传统占卜，但是没有传统元素，求卜人仍然可以为自己读牌, 特别是在路上, 现代生活和过去大不相同.&lt;p>
	&lt;p>当其他应用程序寻求简单地复制塔罗牌，TarotBot旨在发展一种新媒体的塔罗牌的经验.&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>塔罗牌是最有效的读取方式是一个人用直觉来解释每张牌, 我们也功解析来供帮助的不熟悉塔罗牌的人. 这是仍在研究开发过程中进行的工作. 初步研究来源包括:&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>在甲骨文的塔罗牌 由保罗福斯特案例&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>塔罗平原和简单 由安东尼路易&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>学习塔罗牌 由琼邦宁&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>性别魔术, 密宗, 和塔罗牌 由克里斯托弗凯悦&lt;/p>
	&lt;p>甲板包含在免费版本是复古骑士-韦特甲板 通过与艺术品帕梅拉史密斯科尔曼, 作为扫描冬青排球&lt;/p>
</string>
</resources>
